World Federation of Trade Unions Records 5595
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Federation Syndicale Mondiale (FSM): Rencontre Syndicale Internationale a l'occasion du 25eme anniversaire de la Conference Syndicale Mondiale de Londres, 1970-01-30-1970-02-01 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- International Trade Union meeting on the occasion of the 25th anniversary of the London World Trade Union Conference - Conclusions of Brother Pierre Gensous, General Secretary of the WFTU, 1970-01-30-1970-02-01 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- International Trade Union meeting on the present problems of trade union unity and the lessons in unity from the 1945 conference - Introductory speech - Pierre Gensous, General Secretary, WFTU, 1970-01-30-1970-02-01 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Session of the (Executive) Bureau, 1970-02-24-1970-02-26 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Documents adopted by the WFTU Bureau at its meeting in Khartoum, February 24-26, 1970, 1970-03-04 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Meeting of European Trade Union Centres affiliated to the WFTU - Report - Presented by Brother Sandro Stimuli, Secretary of the WFTU, 1970-06-25-1970-06-26 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Federation Syndicale Mondiale: Service Europe - Queloues considerations sur le cadre economique et social, sur la nature, la signification et les perspectives des luttes ouvriers en Europe en 1969, 1970-06 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- 2nd session of the WFTU Bureau - 2nd point on the agenda - Report on the development of the WFTU's activity in Asia - Speaker: Mehendra Sen, Secretary of the WFTU, 1970-10-08-1970-10-10 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- 2nd session of the WFTU Bureau - General Outline Work - Program of the WFTU for improved implementation of the policies adopted at the 7th World Trade Union Congress, 1970-10-08-1970-10-10 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- List of documents adopted by the 2nd session of the WFTU Bureau, 1970-10-08-1970-10-09 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- 20th Session of the WFTU General Council - Report on the first item on the agenda - The WFTU's responsibilities in increasing and strengthening unity amongst trade unions for the satisfaction of the worker's demands and aspirations - Speaker: Pierre Gensous, General Secretary, WFTU, 1970-10-13-1970-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- 20th Session of the WFTU General council - Account of the WFTU's Activity from the 7th Congress (1969) to the General council (1970), 1970-10-13-1970-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- List of documents adopted by the 20th session of the WFTU General Council, 1970-10-13-1970-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- 20th Session of the WFTU General Council - Conclusions of Brother Pierre Gensous, General Secretary of the WFTU, 1970-10-13-1970-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- 3rd session of the WFTU Bureau - 1st item on the agenda - Speech - '100 years ago in Paris a new dawn was born for the international working class: the Paris commune' Speaker: Benoit Frachon, President of the CGT, 1971-04-21-1971-04-23 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  2 mimeographed page typescript
- 3rd session of the WFTU Bureau - 2nd item on the agenda - Report on the main aspects of the development of the situation since the General Council and the tasks arising therefrom for the WFTU - Speaker: Pierre Gensous, General Secretary, WFTU, 1971-04-21-1971-04-23 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  23 page typescript
- 3rd session of the WFTU Bureau - 3rd item on the agenda - Report on the activities of the WFTU and the TUIs and the national affiliated centres at the United Nations with particular reference to the ILO - Speaker: Ibrahim Zakaria, Secretary of the WFTU, 1971-04-21-1971-04-23 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  21 page typescript
- 3rd session of the WFTU Bureau - Conclusions drawn by Pierre Gensous, General Secretary, WFTU on the 2nd and 3rd items, 1971-04-21-1971-04-23 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Report on the study days on multinational companies, 1971-04-26-1971-04-27 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- General Secretary's conclusions and documents adopted at the 3rd session of the WFTU Bureau, 1971-04-28 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- 21st session of the WFTU General Council - 1st item on the agenda - Report " The present aspects of the international trade union movement and the resultant tasks for the WFTU, 1971-12-11-1971-12-13 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Federation Syndicale Mondiale (FSM): 21eme session du Conseil General de la FSM - 2eme point a l'ordre du jour - Rapport sur l'activite des UIS, 1971-12-10-1971-12-13 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Federation Syndicale Mondiale (FSM): 21eme session du Conseil General de la FSM - 3eme point a l'ordre du jour - Rapport sur la presse et propagande de la FSM, 1971-12-10-1971-12-13 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Information Report on the Consultive meeting regarding the work ta the ILO, 1972-02-28 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Account of the first meeting between representatives of special institutes and centers of trade union studies and the WFTU within the framework of future reciprocal cooperation in the light of the 8th World Trade Union Congress, 1972-09-08-1972-09-09 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Document on the monetary crisis - Prepared by the WFTU's working group, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- 22nd session of the WFTU General Council - Account of activities of the WFTU between October 1971 and September 1972, 1972-10-31-1972-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- 22nd session of the WFTU General Council - Report on the meeting of the WFTU delegation with the Secretary-General of the United Nations and on its other meetings and consultations, 1972-11-01-1972-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- 22nd session of the WFTU General Council - First item on the agenda - Report The main problems of international trade union movement in the recent period, consequent work in coming months and especially in view of the 8th World Trade Union Congress, 1972-11-01-1972-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- 22nd session of the General Council Information on the meeting of the Working Group on the problems of working women, 1972-11-01-1972-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Conclusions of Pierre Gensous, WFTU General Secretary at the 22nd session of the WFTU General Council, 1972-11-01-1972-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- 22nd session of the WFTU General Council - (Resolutions; Decisions and appeals,), 1972-11-01-1972-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Document for Bureau members for the discussing of the preparations for the 8th World Trade Union Congress at the 6th session of the WFTU Bureau, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- 8th World Trade Union Congress (WTUC) - Information concerning WFTU's activity in the field of trade union education in Asia Africa and Latin America between the seventh and eight WTUC - Speaker: I. Zakaria, WFTU Secretary, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- 8th WTUC - Charter of the trade union rights and economic and social demands of the present time - Draft, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  41 page mimeographed typescript
- CGIL's proposed amendments to the constitution of the WFTU at the 8th WTUC, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  3 page mimeographed typescript
- Opening speech for the 8th WTUC - Speaker: Pierre Gensous, WFTU General Secretary, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  34 page mimeographed typescript
- 8th WTUC - Policy document (draft), 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- 8th WTUC - (draft) Co-Report on Asia - Speaker: S.A. Dange, Member, WFTU Bureau, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- 8th WTUC - (draft) Co-Report on Latin America - Speaker: Lazaro Pena, Member, WFTU Bureau, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- 8th WTUC (draft) - Co-report on the situation in Africa presented by Vilon Gubzo, Member, WFTU Bureau, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- 8th WTUC - (draft) Co-Report on Europe - Speaker: Georges Seguy, CGT General Secretary, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- 8th World Trade Union Congress (WTUC) - Co-Report on the Middle East by Elias Habre, President of the National trade Union Federation of Lebanese Workers and Employees (FENASOL), 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- 8th WTUC - Report on activities and plans of the Working Group on Young Workers - Speaker: H. Sinno, Chairman of the Working Group, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Federation Syndicale Mondiale: VIIIeme Congress Syndicale Mondiale - Information du groups de travail des Ingenieurs, Cadres et Technicians - Rapporteur: Rene Le Guen, President du Group de Travail, 1973-10-15-1973-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 37)